<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Suraj Kushwah</title>
    <link>http://bugswriter.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Suraj Kushwah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 05:23:48 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://bugswriter.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time to move on FreeBSD</title>
      <link>http://bugswriter.com/blog/time-to-move-on-freebsd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bugswriter.com/blog/time-to-move-on-freebsd/</guid>
      <description>What is FreeBSD? First of all FreeBSD or any BSD is not Linux or its distro. According to freebsd.org -
 FreeBSD is an operating system used to power modern servers, desktops, and embedded platforms. A large community has continually developed it for more than thirty years. Its advanced networking, security, and storage features have made FreeBSD the platform of choice for many of the busiest web sites and most pervasive embedded networking and storage devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Blog</title>
      <link>http://bugswriter.com/blog/first-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bugswriter.com/blog/first-blog/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my blog So today at mid night, I am writing this blog and I am very excited about it. Because this is my first blog on my website. I always wanted this. My own place on &amp;ldquo;The Internet&amp;rdquo;, where I can write whatever I want. I don&amp;rsquo;t like getting censored. This is the main reason why I chose to write here, instead of structuring my rant into 280 character on twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://bugswriter.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bugswriter.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Little bit about me Hi, I am Suraj Kushwah, aka bugswriter. I am 22 old guy from India, who love Computers and Softwares. I am also a Computer Science Student and a Linux Youtuber.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://bugswriter.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://bugswriter.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Here are my contacts   Email: suraj@bugswriter.com
 Don&amp;rsquo;t try to chat on email. Don&amp;rsquo;t expect fast response. I read all emails, so please don&amp;rsquo;t resend.    Telegram: @bugswriter
 I am very active on Telegram. But don&amp;rsquo;t expect quick replies. Try not to ask issues you are getting in your system.    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
